Pensionarea eroilor
Dacă eroii care au salvat lumea
și-ar fi putut găsi liniștea,
misiunea lor ar fi luat sfârșit.
Dar aceștia au fost denunțați și condamnați la moarte de către cei pe care-i salvaseră.
Oamenii au spus că nu
mai aveau nevoie de ei.
Dar asta este nedrept.
Eroii care au săvârșit fapte legendare
nu ar trebui să aibă parte
de o moarte așa de crudă.
Dacă mureau cât încă erau eroi,
aceștia revenuau la viață
drept cetățeni obișnuiți.
Reintegrarea eroilor în societate,
asta este treaba Agenției de
Pensioare și Reacomodare a Eroilor.
Eroine gemene?
Da.
Două surori care au fost trimise împreună,
au lucrat împreună și s-au
întors împreună ca eroi.
Serios? Asta chiar e ceva.
Numele surorii mai mari
este Tsuranari Hakua.
Iar sora mai mică este Kougyoku.
Deci de care mă voi ocupa eu?
Tsuranari Hakua
Sora mai mare: Personajul principal
Tsuranari Kougyoku
Sora mai mică: Donatoare
Gemene
mori
Donatoare
Vrăjitoare
crescută în...
Sora mai mare: Personajul principal
Tsuranari Hakua
Sora mai mare? Sau sora mai mică?
Amândouă.
Amândouă?
Da.
Din moment ce e un caz așa de rar, am hotărât ca amândouă să tranziteze împreună la o viață obișnuită.
Iar tu, Uro, te vei ocupa de
această misiune periculoasă.
Decizia a fost unanimă.
Superiorii chiar cred că pot
să-mi dea orice misiune doresc ei?
Nu poți refuza și nici nu te poți scoate.
Mi-ar plăcea să primesc
niște scuze din când în când.
Ceea ce înseamnă că
de acum înainte amândouă veți trăi pe Pământ drept cetățeni obișnuiți.
Aveți vreo întrebare?
Dacă avem vreo întrebare, auzi la el.
Mai întâi, trebuie să faci
o plecăciune, om de rând!
E o lipsă totală de respesc să ne
vorbește de parcă am fi la același rang.
Am mai spus asta, dar nu mai sunteți eroine, ci niște persoane obișnuite.
De acum înainte, va trebui să învățați și să munciți ca restul oamenilor.
Să-i spui unui cavaler că este o
„persoană obșinuită” este foarte enervant.
Dacă eu sunt o persoană obișnuită, atunci tu ce ești? Un vierme?
Sau poate un gunoi?
Nu mă voi schimba!
Sfidătoare ca întotdeauna.
Ei bine, copiii ca tine se adaptează repede la viața de zi cu zi.
Da, sigur.
S-o crezi tu că voi trăi
printre oamenii de rând.
Nu-i așa, surioară?
Cu sabia, armura și
ornamentele pe care le-am făcut,
sora mea va fi mereu un erou...
Nu se va schimba niciodată.
Sunt sigură de asta.
M-am întors!
Vai, am avut atât de multe de făcut la muncă! Dar am dat tot ce am putut!
Uro, pregătește cina!
Felicitări.
Văd că ai tot lucrat full-time în ultimele zile.
Trebuie să adun experiență cât mai repede ca abilitățile mele să treacă la următorul nivel!
Nu pot continua să fiu o bătaie de cap pentru managerul magazinul.
Cât de admirabil.
Și cu mine acolo, atmosfera magazinul s-a îmbunătățit, așa că pot avansa rapid.
Serios?
Și există ceva ce îmi doresc.
Ar trebui să-l pot cumpară
dacă mai strâng puțin.
Nu te suprasolicita muncind.
Ești o persoană obișnuită acum...
Ah, m-am săturat să tot aud asta!
E doar o chestiune de timp.
Se spune că e bine să ai un obiectiv.
Oh, surioară.
Do you want to hear my talk?
Ce crezi că faci?
Unde e mândria ta de erou?
De ce te enervezi?
It's not as though I can avoid
rubbing shoulders with the masses,
dar asta nu înseamnă că
mi-am abandonat mândria.
On the way home from work at the café,
I got a little cake so cutesy you'd squeal!
Nu înțeleg... ce tot spui acolo...
Și care-i treaba cu hainele pe care le porți?
Unde e armura de argint
pe care ți-am dat-o?
Nu, nu, nu, ieșeam prea
mult în evidență cu ea!
De ce nu încerci și tu să ții pasul cu moda?
Sunt tone de haine drăguțe în această lume.
Așa este.
Kougyoku, vino și tu cu noi data viitoare...
Tu să taci!
Cum rămâne cu sabia?
Cea pe care ți-am dat-o!
Ce? Nu știi?
Pământul are acest sistem de legi.
Te vor aresta dacă deții o armă cu o lamă mai lungă de 6 cm.
O lege?
Și pietrele prețioase?
Cum rămâne cu rubinul în
care am pus protecție divină?
Ar ajunge să fie furat dacă l-aș purta!
Asta ar fi periculos.
Nu voi fi împușcată,
deci nu-ți face griji!
Oricum, nu există demoni în această lume,
deci nu am nevoie de protecție divină.
Nu mai ești soa mea.
Așteaptă, Kougyoku.
Ce dorești?
Dă jos acel petic de pe ochi.
Știu că mă poți vedea.
E probabil periculos să nu ai percepția exactă a distanței.
Mai taci!
Care-i treaba cu atitudinea ei?
Uro, grăbește-te și pregătește cina.
Iar podeaua e udă! Curăț-o!
Nu vii să iei cina?
Nu-ți place friptura cu ghimbir?
E foarte bună.
Faci o armă?
E ceva în neregulă cu asta?
Nu, asta e ceea ce ai
făcut întreaga ta viață.
Zilele trec, iar tu continui
să lucrezi în atelier,
făcând arme, armuri
și accesorii protective.
Totul pentru Hakua.
Hei, nu ți-a fost greu?
Indiferent cât de multă muncă ai depus în crearea armelor,
singura care a primit onoare și laude a fost eroina Hakua, nu?
Ei bine...
Chiar dacă tu ești cea care
ia dat putere lui Hakua,
nimeni nu ți-a oferit atenție.
Continui să oferi,
dar nu primești nimic în schimb.
Asta e soarta unui personaj secundar.
Când mulțimea vorbește de Hakua, săbiile si armurile mele sunt incluse.
Asta e mândria mea.
Nu am nevoie de altceva.
Și de asta îmi e atât de greu s-o iert pe Hakua că s-a schimbat.
Dând de o parte toate lucrurile pe care le-am făcut cu atât de multă grijă,
pentru o „slujbă part-time” sau „modă”!
De ce vrei să mi-o schimbi pe Hakua?
Yamada Uro!
Asta e slujba mea.
Exact cum tu ai transformat-o pe Hakua într-un erou, eu voi vă face pe voi două niște simpli cetățeni.
Eu nu mă voi schimba!
Sunt sigură de asta.
Și îți voi arăta că o face
pe Hakua un erou din nou!
Hei, sabia aia e complet îndoită.
Asta e dovada că nu te
uiți la ce e în fața ta.
Nu poți face o armă astfel.
Spre deosebire de lumea în care vrei să fii,
aici nu poți folosi magia atât de ușor.
Dacă vrei să devii un meșteșugar în această lume, cel mai bine ar fi s-o iei de la zero...
Dacă o folosesc astfel, e o armă.
Hmpf!
B-Bine...
Districtul Barurilor
Tsuranari Kougyoku. Fost meșteșugar.
Un erou creator de obiecte care și-a folosit întreaga putere pentru sora ei mai mare.
Se pare că încă e blocată într-un vis.
Iar acel vis e probabil...
De ce arăți atât de posomorât?
You can't forgive the world that takes
the sister that she gave her all to,
and turns her into something mediocre, isn't she just the model younger sister?
Vai, cât de inocent...
E ceva de admirat să ai visuri.
Dar mi-ar plăcea dacă ar renunța la visurile ei care depind de o altă persoană.
I can't believe she's entrusting her
entire worth as a person to her sister...
She's a fool.
Do you think we should try to arrange a little get-together?
Get-together?
Assemble Alice and the heroes you've worked with so far at the beach,
and let Kougyoku-chan meet
someone other than Hakua-san.
You can count on me to be there to help.
That's a pretty good idea,
but you're not just asking because
you want to see girls in swimsuits, are you?
I refuse to confirm or deny my motivations.
Don't try and hide your fetishes.
We'll relax on the beach in the afternoon, and have barbecue for dinner.
Then, with full stomachs,
we'll have fun with fireworks.
It's a good chance for you to get to know each other better.
Hakua, Kyogyoku, say hello.
Aye.
To be honest, I thought this was a pain,
but as long as I'm here I plan to have fun.
I'm counting on you all.
Come on, you too, say hello.
Wow, I bet it'll be a lot of fun!
I can't wait to eat some barbecue!
Karon-san's as energetic as ever!
But to be sure, this is a great chance for us to
meet new people and strengthen our relationships.
Don't you think? Airo-san.
Not really.
If I have to say one way or the other, this feels like a bother to me.
I hate the heat.
Little one, remember to
play nice with your friends.
Since when have you been my mother, Alice?
Oh my. You don’t have to call me your mother, "young lady" will do fine.
Take this!
Killer technique,
Ultra No-Way-In-Hell Super Spike!
With an exceedingly lame attack name like that, there's no way you could defeat me, Karon!
Which means, it's my turn!
Miracle Hyper Jump-Powered Smash!
Alright, I did it!
To think I couldn't stop it at this range...
Working part-time all night might be hard,
but I haven't felt this kind of indignity since I was a hero!
How irritating!
Working part-time all night sure is hard.
When you're tired,
you can't summon any strength.
However. That physical
limitation is a good thing!
Striving to reach new heights,
dealing with a body that refuses to do as it's told...
Yes, yes, your will may be broken harder than your body in the end, but even so!
Buckling down and refusing to give in
creates its own kind of
light at the end of the tunnel!
Things aren't going to go as you expect.
But it's because you can't reach
those heights that life is interesting!
At first glance, you seemed dim-witted,
and your speech appeared foolishly blunt,
but you say can some rather deep things.
I don't mind if you start looking up to me.
I may be impertinent
and arrogant, but I like you.
Now that we're friends, why don't we run off into the sunset together?!
It's midday as hell right now, but I concur!
Where did they learn that kind of meat-headed communication?
Honestly, just looking at them is sweltering.
My, my, isn't it a good thing?
Blending bodies and heat,
their hearts move as one.
That kind of communication is lovely!
I-If you say so...
Yes! Of course, I also love the quiet bonding we are sharing right now.
There are many ways of
interacting with other people.
After all, there are so
many people in this world!
Reca-san, you have such a big heart.
As one would expect of a former princess.
There are times where I can't quite say the same about myself
I know it's not good, but...
Wait.
Why are the decorations all Rococo?
Didn't we decide on a Gothic style?
Well, it's because I like swirly things!
Airo-san, you're too picky about your scenery!
Wh—what's that supposed to mean?
This kind of thing works out best when you stick to the plan!
My, my, if you get that upset about it,
you're just as bad as Karon-san!
You're absolutely mistaken!
I'll tell Uro-kun about this!
Hey, wouldn't you agree?
How would I know?
Beautiful former heroes
in swimsuits! And the ocean!
Is this paradise?
What a peaceful scene!
That's right, peaceful.
Apart from you being here.
She can't fit in with them, huh.
That girl... she reminds me a lot of how you were long ago.
Really?
Yes, she's just like you.
What are you saying?
Compared to Uro-san,
Kougyoku-chan is way, way cuter!
Four-eyes, you're getting on my nerves.
You want things that are important to you to remain important.
That's why you can't accept new things.
You become obstinate and close in on yourself.
That's just like you!
You can say she's like me, but you shouldn't treat her that way.
Yes, I know that.
I won't tease her.
Well, maybe just a little.
It does make me want to... stir things up.
Everything tastes better
when you eat outside!
Uro, more alcohol.
You're drinking too much.
Kougyoku-san!
Perfectly-done meat, just for you!
The truth is, I've been aiming to talk to you since this afternoon,
but I became too caught
up frolicking with Hakua-san.
Kougyoku-san, let's be friends too!
What a pain.
Woah, rejected! I just got hit with a clear, outright rejection!
This time, it was your own fault.
Honestly, heroes sure have such bad manners, it's a problem.
Woah, from the witch too!
Let this loud one be,
and let's relax and talk over there, just us two support characters.
You're a pain too.
Oi, Kougyoku!
Stop it already! You've
got to try to communicate or—
Shut up!
What do you mean, "friends"?
What do you mean, "communication"?
Why do you get along with them?!
You're a hero, aren't you?!
What have you been so
unhappy about this whole time?
Everyone's going out of their way to have fun.
That's it! It's because of that that you're—
I have no idea what
my younger sister is thinking.
I'm going to check on her.
Okay.
Kougyoku!
Unde ești?
Seriously, where could she have gone?
Alice went after her, so I'm sure it's nothing too extreme, but...
That is something to
be worried about, isn't it.
She's bound to be up to something,
that old monster.
She does tend to play
some nasty tricks sometimes.
She's overloaded with cuteness.
Kougyoku!
Hei, Uro.
Sper că nu este supărată pe noi Kougyoku.
Airo?
I kind of understand her feelings.
As support characters, no matter how hard we try, we can't get the glory.
That's why we get so
picky about certain things.
What's really important to her is probably...
Don't worry. She won't be mad.
I'm sure Hakua understands that too.
But where could Kougyoku-san be—
Honestly.
What could she possibly be
talking about, that sister of mine?
All my plans have gone down the drain!
Hakua!
I finished a new gem!
It's full of protection!
As long as you have this, you're invincible!
Good grief, she's so troublesome!
Kougyoku!
Încă nu am reușit s-o găsim...
And where did that meat-head go?
And four-eyes, too.
If Karon-san's gone too, then that means...
Well, it is Alice.
Airo-san?
This is bad! Reca! Stay close to me!
Alice! Kougyoku!
I know you're there!
"We have the heroes. If you want them back, come to the beach!"
Yamada Uro!
Send Hakua and me back to our world!
Alice. What's this about?
Just helping out a woman
with something to say.
I'm here to test you, anytime, anywhere.
I don't suppose I could get you to
stop putting my life on Hard Mode?
Don't ignore me!
Send us back immediately!
Hey, Kougyoku. You made that
crossbow by yourself, didn't you.
You can't shoot with that.
It's not held together well, and it's crooked.
I'm sorry, but as long as
you can't accept this world,
you can't craft anything.
Taci!
Cu ce drept spui asta?
Crafting things in this
world is a very difficult thing.
As long as you're not looking
properly at the things in front of you,
you can't make anything.
Why?
Why do you get in my way?
I just love the hero Hakua,
I want to make things for her
so she can be praised,
and free, and strong... that's all.
You stupid little sister!
Become the greatest craftsperson in this world,
too! This time, without any magic!
Kougyoku!
Hakua...
I was planning for a situation
where you were more excited,
but that's not a big deal anymore.
Here. It's a present for you.
Why...
Hakua's been working so hard at her part-time job to buy this for you.
Day in and day out, living a life she couldn't get used to...
Well, I can do anything if I put my mind to it.
Why...
why would you do something like that for me?
I'm a supporting character.
It's my job to give you—
What are you being so
picky about? Sister of mine.
I received so much from
you back in the other world.
This time it's my turn to give.
Earn money through dealing with people.
I'll take on the daily tasks of a hero.
That way you can put your whole
heart into mastering craftsmanship.
But that means you—
Who do you think I am?
In the other world
I was one of the greatest hero.
And in this world...
I'm your only sister.
And—
Woah!
you ought to be a little fashionable too.
Just like me, you can't
let your beauty go to waste.
Surioară...
Surioară!
Give me a sparkler!
Me too!
Come on, wait your turn!
That girl's just like you after all.
You keep saying that, but in what way?
Whenever she decides something's important, she won't let go no matter what happens.
Yes, very stubborn.
Ah, when you put it that way, I kind of—
Hey, Karon! Don't wave the
sparkler around! That's dangerous!
Somebody let me down...
With that matter settled, it's so much fun to fireworks with everyone!
You were easily captured
pretty early on, weren't you?
You sure are the kind of witch that little kids worry about.
Ce ai spus?
Haide să mai aprindem una!
Hei, așteaptă!
Oh, am pierdut din nou!
Ura, șapte la rând!
Asta e surioara mea!
Nu o voi pierde pe următoarea!
Tot eu voi câștiga!
Și voi face opt puncte!
Ce briză plăcută.
Nu credeți că există și lucruri
frumoase în această lume?
Ba da!
A page of the brilliant everyday
îmi prezice viitorul
Iluzia, care mi-a fost oferită, se face nevăzută în ceață
Cutreier prin acest peisaj lipsit de culoare
de parcă nu mai știu cine sunt
Sunt mereu singura
care poate proteja această luminiță și ultimă speranță
Mă întreb dacă amintirea cu noi, cântând pe acel deal,
va dănui până la finalul timpului
Strălucind precum un diamant
O lumină puternică
ne arată viitorul